[ 480p & 720p Movies Download | Mkvking.com]
Hey Harby.
- Did you find anything good today?
- It's all garbage.
Tower! Tower!
Plane to tower:
we're taking off!
Is this all?
I have a shipment coming in later.
Very funny.
- What happened to your foot?
- Workplace accident.
- Take this.
- That's all?
Give me more, man.
That's all I have today.
I should sell my goods
to the Pachas of Cairo.
Bring me some fancy coffee beans
on your way back.
Tell the Pachas I said hello!
Greetings, sick people!
Hello, Beshay!
Easy, doc. It hurts.
It's probably broken. I have to
use the machine to be sure.
You need a permit from
the manager to use it.
Can't you just do it now?
I'm sorry, Beshay. I can't.
You need a permit.
Come in, Om Hassan.
That referee was a crook!
He blew two penalties,
one against us!
Greetings.
- How are you, Beshay?
- I want to get this signed.
What happened?
I need an x-ray for my foot.
You should be more careful.
- Last name?
- Qenawi.
Signature.
Get this signed by Dr. Ahmed.
Do I have to see him?
Yes.
We had a great ref last time,
not like that crook!
Enter.
Greetings.
How are you, Beshay?
I had an accident.
How is work?
It's alright.
And your wife?
She is better now, don't you agree?
My house is empty since you sent her away.
She was a threat to your neighbors.
I promise to bring her back
when she gets better.
She was fine when
she took her medicine.
Leave it to God.
Sign this paper!
Okay.
Ready to visit Ireny, Harby?
- Greetings, sick people!
- Hello, Beshay!
Obama!
Where are you going, Beshay?
To see Ireny.
Take me with you.
Just meet me at
Garbage Mountain tomorrow!
Come, Beshay.
How are you doing, Ireny?
It's nice here, right?
Clean food and drink, a nice clean bed.
Look what I found.
I'll turn it on for you.
I'll fix it and bring it back.
When you're better,
we'll go far away from here.
And I'll get you whatever you want.
This kid just needs a bath.
Take him under your wing, boss.
He'll be my right hand man.
Obama, you little buffalo.
There you are!
How are you, Beshay?
Thanks be to God.
Have a tea with us.
I'm just here for the kid.
Let's go, Obama.
Tell me, Beshay...
How is your crazy wife?
You should get yourself a new one.
No man —
Christians can only get married once.
Really? I had no idea.
I told you not to sit with those thugs.
I came early but you weren't here.
- Why aren't you at school?
- It's Friday.
- Then why aren't you at the mosque?
- You asked me to come early.
- I said that?
- Yes.
Obama!
What?
Come read this to me.
This is English.
Don't they teach you English in school?
Only things like
"Welcome to Egypt" and "I love you".
Look how yellow her hair is!
- Who's that guy?
- I don't know.
You'd know if you paid attention in school.
You can't even read!
Shut up, you buffalo.
Beshay!
Hello, Bomba!
- Where have you been?
- Right here.
- Dr. Ahmed sent me.
- What's up?
He told me you were here.
And here I am.
Condolences.
Condolences, Beshay.
There's no judgement for the
mentally ill. She's in Heaven.
You sent her to get cured,
and she came back in a coffin.
Leave it to God.
Fine.
Do you need anything, Beshay?
Thanks, guys.
Stay strong. Let's go.
Stay strong, Beshay.
How's Beshay today, Harby?
Beshay.
- What are you doing here?
- Making sure you're okay.
Why aren't you at school?
We got the day off
because a sewer pipe exploded.
Liar.
Loosen up, Beast.
Don't call me Beast.
What happened to your ear?
Nothing. The kids at the
orphanage beat me up.
- Is she coming over here?
- Looks like it.
- Are you Beshay?
- Yes. Can I help you?
I'm Ireny's mother.
I didn't know she had a family.
Everyone has a family.
If I had a family, I'd look for them.
Forgive me, Lord.
I never came to visit her.
Who told you she died?
The colony administration
sent me a telegram.
What?
Can I do anything for you?
Have dinner with us.
I'm sorry, I still have a long way to go.
Mr. Reda!
- I want to see my file.
- What file?
- My papers!
- Calm down, have a seat.
How did you contact my wife's family?
We usually contact them upon death
in case they want to bury them in their village.
Why didn't you contact them
when she was alive?
No one ever answers.
I don't think you have a file.
- How did you get here?
- My father left me here.
Did he leave you at the gate
or bring you inside?
- Outside.
- Alright then!
Your wife was registered
when she arrived. You weren't.
Come, eat.
I have work to do.
Don't be upset. No one here
knows their family.
You really thought you had a file?
I thought I'd try.
And do what? Call them?
"Hello Papa, come pick me up. I'm at the door."
Nice one.
None of you want to know
where your families are?
At my age, it would be a miracle if
I still had a family that cared about me.
How old are you?
40, I think.
Where are you from?
Abuhoor, in Qena.
Maybe thirty years ago
you had a chance to reconnect.
You think they'll remember you now?
Let's say you do have a family.
How are you going to get to them?
You're a leper.  No one
will let you ride a car or a train.
Do you even have any
money left after the funeral?
You'll end up dead under a bridge.
Am I right, guys?
That's right.
I'm serious, man.
God blessed you all with children.
They'll keep your memory alive
when you die.
But when I die, no one
will remember me.
Get out!
Goodbye, sick people.
Beshay!
Did you forget about me?
- Why aren't you at school?
- School is closed.
- Go play at the orphanage.
- With who?
At the orphanage.
Are you going to Garbage Mountain?
None of your business.
What's all this stuff?
I said go play at the orphanage!
What's wrong?
Good morning, Beshay.
Son of a —
Wait! Where are you going?
Wait, Beshay!
Wait, man.
Look.
We're here.
This is the Nile.
Here's Qena.
Stay on the main road until
you reach the Nile.
Keep going south from there
until you reach Qena.
That's all I know.
Take care of yourself.
Goodbye, Beshay.
Hello!
Where's the Nile?
The Nile? Up your ass.
What are these donkeys laughing at?
No offense, Harby.
Hello!
I'm telling you we have a flat tire.
He's fixing it but I'll be late.
Where are we, Harby?
Did we reach the Pyramids?
Obama, you buffalo. Get out!
What are you doing here?
I didn't want to be alone.
Didn't I leave you at the orphanage? Go back!
You're still here?
I said leave!
Fine. Come.
Always trouble with you.
Don't finish it.
There isn't enough.
- Are these the Pyramids?
- I don't know.
Aren't there three?
Where are the other two?
I don't know!
- Where are you going?
- None of your business.
What's that?
A tomb for the King and Queen.
Is this for the King's wife?
I think so.
Beshay!
What are you doing up there?
You'll fall.
- Get down!
- Okay.
Come on, you buffalo.
What are you doing, Obama?
What does it say?
Probably a love note.
Don't ruin the antiquities.
Beshay.
What?
Is everyone in Qena
called Qenawi?
No.
They gave you that name
at the colony?
Yes.
- What if you're from Gharbeya?
- Gharbawi.
What if you're from Cairo?
Cairo people don't get leprosy.
What's your real last name?
Selim.
They call me the Nubian.
I was in an orphanage in Sohag,
then they transferred me.
I was happy there.
You're looking for your family, right?
Yes.
Damn it.
Come on, Obama. Hurry up!
There's the Nile!
It's pretty.
Beshay!
- What do you want?
- Come.
- Come and swim.
- No.
Are you afraid or what?
Just come on, the water's great!
How long since your last shower?
You're contaminating our water!
Cows are in it too,
what's the difference?
You'll infect our children!
Your kids have water worms!
Let's go, kids!
Are you mad at
what the woman said?
No, I know I'm a leper.
Don't pull too hard.
Come on, Obama.
Obama!
Answer me!
Help!
- Is there a hospital here?
- There's a clinic down the road.
The boy is hurt.
- Step back.
- Why?
Because I said so.
I said step back!
What are you afraid of?
Samah, come here!
He's in pain.
Your ID.
- What?
- I need your ID.
I don't have it.
- What's the boy's name?
- Obama.
Obama.
Are you a relative?
I'm his father.
20 pounds.
I left my money at the beach.
- Go and get it then.
- Okay.
Don't forget your ID.
Excuse me, officer.
Get that man.
You there!
Come and talk to the officer.
- Why are you dressed like that?
- I was swimming.
- Where are your clothes?
- At the beach.
- Why did you leave them?
- I was saving the boy.
- Where is your ID?
- Also at the beach.
- The beach?
- Yes, with my clothes.
You make me come back
every day for new requests!
I told you I need proof of residence.
I need my card for that!
I need to see the kid.
God damn you, Obama!
I left the kid behind.
Sir!
I need to see the kid.
Wait for the officer!
Excuse me.
How long are they
going to keep us here?
Did they arrest you
for lewd conduct?
I don't know.
- What's that?
- What?
Officer!
Keep him away from me!
What's wrong, man?
Be quiet, with your scabies!
It's not scabies, it's leprosy.
It's not contagious anymore.
I'm cured.
Lord help me.
And what are you in here for?
Did they catch you stealing
or in a brothel?
Officer! My boy is in the hospital,
I need to see him.
- What's wrong with him?
- Just everyday scum.
He looks like a hammered nail.
I don't want him in here.
Mohamed! Take them downstairs.
Give me your hands.
Come here, Khaled.
Why?
You're coming too.
What's wrong with you people?
You don't fear God?
No respect for anything.
Walk. Let's go.
We're on our own.
- My Quran!
- What?
- I forgot my Quran.
- I'll bring it later.
I'm not moving without my Quran!
It's enough you're
holding me without charge!
Calm down, I'll get it!
When I say run, you run.
- What?
- Run!
Go get him!
- Run, man!
- What a shitty day!
Thanks.
Why are there so many of you?
That's why they keep
throwing us in prison.
"Run from a leper
as you would run from a lion."
How could I run
if I'm shackled to him?
So lepers are like lions?
- Are you making fun of the Prophet?
- Not at all.
He didn't mean it.
Tell me...
What's your name?
Mohamed.
Mohamed?
Alright.
Fine. "Mohamed".
Yes?
Don't you have to see your kid?
Wait! Are you going
dressed like that?
- How are you?
- Good.
How did you get away?
I ran.
Always trouble with you.
The money is gone!
Are you happy now?
You made me swim
and now my money is gone.
I'm sorry.
I told you I don't swim.
- Nothing to say?
- I said I'm sorry.
What do I do with you now?
What?
Should we go back to the colony?
Why?
We have nothing left.
150 pounds wasn't
going to get us far anyway.
What about your injury?
I'll survive.
Hurry up, before the disease sticks to us.
Listen, Beshay. I'll leave you here.
They will take care of you.
And when you're cured,
I'll come and get you.
Take care of yourself.
We have to leave!
What the hell are you doing?
Are you feeling better?
I invented something.
- What's this?
- Try it on.
So people don't get scared of you.
You can take it off when we're alone.
You look good!
Fine.
Stop it, you little shit.
Stop it, Obama.
Hold on.
Where are you going?
Come on.
- I don't know how to dance.
- Just come on!
Beans again?
What would your Highness
like for breakfast?
- I want meat!
- Then let's eat Harby.
No, no!
Beans are fine!
Greetings!
Let's see what they want.
We need to fix our pump.
Can you take us with you?
Where are you going?
South.  Isn't that on your way?
Yes.
May the Lord lighten your way.
Let's go, boy!
Help me, Lord!
May the Lord protect you.
What would we do without you.
We need to take the ferry
to cross the Nile.
- Where are you going?
- Qena.
- On this cart?
- Yes.
Bless your heart.
Have a safe trip.
- Tickets.
- We don't have money.
Don't worry, I got this.
How much is it, buddy?
We're three days away from Qena.
But it's late now.
Spend the night with us.
Thank you.
Almost there.
A little further.
Come on!
Stop, thief!
Thief!
Obama, stay with Harby!
Are you okay, Harby?
Don't touch me!
- Whose shack is this?
- It belongs to the group.
- What group?
- Don't touch me!
Let's go.
What happened?
Let's go before the rest show up.
Let's get out of this stink.
Hey.
Tickets.
Let's get out of here.
Wait a second.
Tickets.
Two... tickets.
- What?
- Two!
- To where?
- To Qena.
Ten pounds.
I don't have any money.
You don't have money?
You want to ride for free?
- No.
- Then what?
I lost my money.
- Then get off.
- Take your hands off me!
Don't push him!
Mind your own business.
What's your problem?
Get away!
I'm a human being!
Harby is tired.
Stay strong, Harby.
We're almost there.
Oh, Harby...
Tickets.
What's wrong, Harby?
Please don't die!
I beg you, Harby!
Don't die!
Do animals get judged
on Judgment Day?
No.
They go straight to Heaven.
Excuse me, sir.
What's up, Hajj?
I'm sorry to disturb you.
Where are we?
Are you kidding? You're in Sohag.
We want to go to Qena.
I don't know how to help you.
Can I get anything
so I can feed the boy?
May God help you.
Please.
Sorry, man.
Got any change?
Hey, you!
You, over there!
What are you doing here?
You son of a bitch!
Are you talking to me?
Who else!
What are you doing here?
I'm standing.
This is my corner.
I didn't know.
There are rules to begging!
I'm sorry. I'm not a beggar.
Oh, did I hurt your feelings?
Take the boy and leave. Go!
Fine.
Sorry. We're not beggars.
Every day there's trouble.
Screw the whole world.
Let's go.
What?
I can't leave you with a sick kid.
Where to?
A five star hotel.
Don't worry. You don't have
anything I can steal.
- Does this hurt?
- No.
This only hurts when I've
been on my feet all day.
I'm joking, stupid.
You're a little slow, aren't you?
I told him "Get out of my area before
I let the rabid dogs loose."
Why rabid dogs? Just use Mouth.
Let them make some money.
They're new here.
Did you forget what I did to you, Mouth?
I'd have punched you
in the face if I could reach it.
You could reach his balls, though.
- Why aren't you laughing?
- Tell me, Beshay...
What brings you here from up North?
We're going to Qena.
Why?
To look for my family.
Where in Qena?
A place called Abuhoor.
Where is that?
Somewhere in Qena.
You've never been there?
As a child.
How will you get there?
I'll ask.
Let's see your face.
- Take it easy on him, Mouth.
- Leave him alone.
What's the difference?
We're all freaks!
It's not contagious, right?
No.
How long have you been like this?
Since I was a child.
Did you scare the other kids?
When I got hurt while playing
I wouldn't feel pain.
So they called me Beast.
It turned out I had leprosy.
The Beast was just a Leper.
Damn, that's deep.
At the colony they told me, if you
leave you'll end up under a bridge.
But it's not so bad down here.
We live like kings!
We are happy you are here.
The boy is not your son.
No.
What's his story?
He never leaves my side.
What about his family?
He doesn't have one.
He was in an orphanage here
in Sohag before they moved him.
Was he happy there?
I think so.
Maybe he'd like to visit his old home.
Why?
Why are you going home?
That's different.
My father promised me.
He said he would come back.
Obama was never promised anything.
I don't want him
to feel ashamed of himself.
You see Hamed over there?
He used to be a truck driver.
Big trailer trucks.
Drove everywhere.
Libya, Tunisia, Sudan.
Then he had an accident.
A young guy in a new car, on drugs.
And Hamed became what he is now.
Mouth, Hamed and me are all
judged by our looks.
We are outcasts.
There's no cure for that.
There is no other life.
Me, you, and the other monsters over there
will never be "normal".
But that doesn't mean we should live in shame.
You think Hamed could have stood up to you
if he was ashamed?
We live on the hope that on Judgment Day
we will all be equal.
That'll be the day.
Might be sooner than you think.
When the boy gets up, tell him
we have a surprise for him.
- Is this it?
- I think so.
It was abandoned after the earthquake.
You're lucky you didn't end up on the street.
- Do you remember?
- I don't know.
Did they beat you here too?
Not as much as up North.
There's no water, but
the toilets are still here.
High quality ceramic
and all that nice stuff.
When did you come here?
I don't remember.
How old are you?
Ten.
Our government is very organized.
They probably didn't have many Nubians.
No, no, no.
God bless Egyptian bureaucracy!
- What's your real name?
- Mohamed.
- Last name?
- Mohamed...
- This one looks like you.
- He doesn't look like Obama at all.
He's just younger here.
And his name is Mohamed.
The whole country is named Mohamed!
Born November 6, 2004 in Kom Ombo.
Did they relocate your ancestors when
they flooded Nubia?
I don't know.
What do they teach you in school?
What's my last name?
Abdelrazek.
- So my name is Mohamed Abdelrazek?
- That's not Obama!
Just let it go!
Do you want to know what
happened to your parents?
No.
Let's go and find your family.
Good job, Agwa.
Work faster. guys!
I said a thousand times they
should send better people.
Good job, Assaleya.
What a shit show.
Baraka!
Good God, let me pray in peace.
Oh, hello!
Hi Baraka.
What a nice surprise.
How are you doing, Baraka?
What brings you here?
- I need a favor.
- Whatever you want.
My friends need to go to Abuhoor.
- Where's that?
- In Qena.
Abdallah!
Yes?
Aren't you doing the Qena route?
Take these people to Abuhoor.
It's out of my way.
They're with Hamed!
Oh, Hamed!
Of course, whatever you want.
How are your legs, Hamed?
They're a little weak today.
This truck will get you there.
Hop on.
Hurry up!
Don't ever beg on my corner again.
Thank you so much.
I don't know what to say.
We'll meet again. Right?
God willing.
Goodbye!
We'll meet again!
I'll have legs then!
Thanks, driver!
- Is this it?
- I don't know.
- The name is right.
- Then it must be it.
- Let's go.
- Let's catch our breath.
How long are we going to wait?
Let's just rest for a moment.
Are you afraid?
Do you want to go back to the colony?
Maybe I should.
After everything we've been through?
Let's go, you coward.
I'm the coward?
How about we read
what happened to your parents!
- Damn you!
- Me?!
Greetings.
Is this the Selim family house?
Who's there?
Greetings.
Is this the Selim family house?
Yes, what is it?
Is Hajj Selim home?
We don't have Hajjis.
This is a Christian home.
I meant the Big Selim.
Who are you?
Mohamed Abdelrazek.
What do you want?
Remember Beshay?
Beshay who?
Your brother.
Are you joking?
Beshay is here to see his father.
Beshay died when we were kids.
He had scabies.
He didn't die. He had leprosy.
Beshay died during treatment up North.
Now leave!
Just give me a minute!
I'm afraid they'll throw me out again.
I asked around.
There is no one left.
Happy now?
At least we got to see the world.
So what happened to my family?
You know I can't read.
"Status of Parents: Deceased."
That's it? I knew that already!
God bless this bur... bureau-cracky.
Egyptian bureau-cracky.
You can't even say it right?
That's the one.
Let's rest tonight and
take the train home in the morning.
They'll kick you off again.
I'll ride with the animals.
Time to pray.
Oh.
Go and pray.
- Do I have to?
- Yes.
What about you?
I'll pray in the back.
I have an allergy.
- Welcome to the club, Hajj.
- Shut up, you buffalo!
I'm going to rest for a bit.
I'll wake you up for the next prayer.
Whatever.
I'm going for a walk.
Fine.
How did you know
Beshay had leprosy?
His father brought him
to the colony.
- What's that?
- A place for lepers.
- They live there?
- Yes.
They don't die?
When they get old.
- So it's like a prison?
- No.
Why didn't he come sooner?
- You're sure it's not contagious?
- I'm healthy, aren't I?
God help us.
How are you, Beast?
No need to cover your face.
Don't be ashamed.
The boy told me you were cured.
From the disease, not the scars.
How did you get here?
I rode everything.
A cart, a donkey...
A donkey?
Where is he?
He died.
We thought you died too.
Come, Beshay.
He had a stroke a few years ago.
His brain doesn't work like it used to.
Leave it.
Did you forget about me?
Do you hate me?
I did it for you.
I didn't come back
because...
Son, I was afraid
that you would look at us
and try to live a life
you're not meant to have
and be bitter.
I gave you a second chance
with people who wouldn't judge you.
You wouldn't have found love here.
"Run from a leper
as you would run from a lion."
I did it for you.
Don't do that, father.
No need for that.
That's enough, thank you!
Welcome.
What's your name?
Obama.
Like the guy on TV.
Take this.
It's a birthday present.
On the 6th of Sep... vember.
Like it says in your papers.
Wasn't it Bovember or Comender?
No, Sittember.
...vember.
Whatever it says in your papers.
What is today's date?
No idea.
What's that sound?
Do you want to live here?
What about you?
My place isn't here.
I have to go back.
My place isn't here either.
Your place is not with sick people.
You're not sick.
You just have scars that don't heal.
Is this what you want?
I want to stay with you.
Where's the damn train?
- Maybe there are no trains.
- Then what are these tracks for?
I miss Garbage Mountain.
Me too.
I miss the colony. The good
people and the bad ones.
All of them.
There it is!
What's that piece of junk?
- When is the real train coming?
- No trains at this station.
Take us to the colony.
- Where?
- The colony!
Hop on!
Let's go! Faster!